Now remember, always use a round brush and a blow dryer after you shampoo your hair.
This will help smooth out the texture of the hair and get any tangles out.
We're going to always make sure that there's no tangles in the hair.
This is just one of the ways that you can straighten your hair.
Now remember, if you like to use a flat iron, you can do so.
You can also use a curling iron.
You simply grab your flat iron and you pull it through your hair.
Nice and slow.
If you don't pull it through nice and slow, you could leave some curl in the hair.
Now remember, this is something that's very easy to do, and it doesn't take a lot of time.
You also can use a blow dryer.
Leave it close to the hair, follow the hair shaft all the way down.
Making sure that you get a nice, smooth texture on the hair.
Also use some shine serums and some sealers to protect the hair.
My name is Sylvia Russell, and this is how you can straighten curly hair.